

Warner Robins, GA

■ andrew.romans@hotmail.com | ★ andrewromans.com | 🖸 aromans | 🛅 andrew-romans

Summary _

Experienced Software Engineer with a passion and focus in Cyber Security, transitioning from a Machine Learning and Simulation background. Proficient in many languages, from C and x86 assembly to Python. Spends free time participating in CTFs, pwning challenges in TryHackMe and HackTheBox, and staying up-to-date with techniques on malware analysis, reverse engineering, and recent cyber threats.

Work Experience _____

 Air Force
 Warner Robins, GA

COMPUTER SCIENTIST

Feb. 2021 - Present

- Led Artificial Intelligence efforts in the 577th of the DCGS.
- Responsible for advising and assisting other team projects on their AI and development efforts, helping teams accomplish their objectives.
- Advised in system architecture design and provided insights on best security practices through development.
- Worked on multi-disciplinary machine learning projects, such as Natural Language Processing, Computer Vision, and Regression prediction.

Shadow Health Gainesville, FL

GAME DEVELOPER

Jan. 2018 - Jun. 2021

- · Led the development of multiple high-fidelity 3D simulations for nursing colleges in over 1,800 programs worldwide.
- · Developed in-house tools for interdisciplinary teams that helped increase team production and streamlined designer workflow.
- · Chaired meetings for maintaining and discussing code and system infrastructure for older and newer simulations.
- · Collaborated with large cross-interdisciplinary teams to communicate, build, and maintain features.

Certifications

Aug 2022 Security+, Credential ID: TKRMB8EYJFBE1X9G

CompTIA

Education

Georgia Institute of Technology

Atlanta, GA

M.S. IN CYBERSECURITY

Jan. 2019 - Present

Kennesaw State University

Kennesaw, GA

B.S. IN COMPUTER GAME DESIGN AND DEVELOPMENT

Aug. 2013 - May. 2017

Security Clearance _____

TS/SCI Feb. 2021 - Present